Something, something, something's wrong with me, I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed, no ghost in my head Something's wrong with me, I'm okay instead
I woke up calm, that's suspicious My hands were steady like, who approved this?
I ate my breakfast, didn't spiral once Now I'm staring at the wall like it's a loaded gun
No panic, no drama, not even a crack I hate how normal keeps looking back
Something's off, something's off, I checked the mirror twice No sirens in my chest, no teeth on the inside
I should be breaking, I should be a mess I'm not self-isolating, I'm here answering texts
Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed, no ghost in my head Something's wrong with me, I'm okay instead
I paid the bill on the first try Didn't lose the keys, didn't start a fight
I laughed out loud at a stupid meme Then I just kept walking like a human being
I know it sounds nice, I know it sounds clean But this kind of peace feels illegal to me
Something's off, something's off, I keep waiting for the drop For the floor to split, for the whole thing to stop
I should be breaking, I should be a mess I'm not self-isolating, I'm here answering texts
Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed, no ghost in my head Something's wrong with me, I'm okay instead
I wanted a rescue, I wanted a sign Now I'm healthy and terrified
By the shape of my mind
Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today Something's wrong with me, I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed, no ghost in my head Something's wrong with me, I'm okay instead