Something's wrong with me
I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed
No ghost in my head
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay instead
I woke up calm
That's suspicious
My hands were steady
Like, who approved this?
I ate my breakfast
Didn't spiral once
Now I'm staring at the wall
Like it's a loaded gun
No panic, no drama
Not even a crack
I hate how normal
Keeps looking back
Something's off, something's off
I checked the mirror twice
No sirens in my chest
No teeth on the inside
I should be breaking
I should be a mess
I'm not self isolating
I'm here answering texts
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed
No ghost in my head
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay instead
I paid the bill
On the first try
Didn't lose the keys
Didn't start a fight
I laughed out loud
At a stupid meme
Then I just kept walking
Like a human being
I know it sounds nice
I know it sounds clean
But this kind of peace
Feels illegal to me
Something's off, something's off
I keep waiting for the drop
For the floor to split
For the whole thing to stop
I should be breaking
I should be a mess
I'm not self isolating
I'm here answering texts
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed
No ghost in my head
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay instead
I wanted a rescue
I wanted a sign
Now I'm healthy and terrified
By the shape of my mind
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay today
No crash, no bleed
No ghost in my head
Something's wrong with me
I'm okay instead